《黑镜》
《黑函之舞》
肯尼 四号桌有东西洒出来了 去处理下吧
Kenny? Big spillage on table four. Sorry.
好的 知道了
Okay. All right.
等一下
Excuse me.
有人忘拿东西了
Someone forgot this.
哦 谢谢
Oh, thank you!
- 你应该说什么 - 谢谢
- What do you say? - Thank you.
- 不客气 - 她总是忘东西 再次感谢
- It's all right. - She forgets everything. Thanks again.
她是个瑜伽老师 身体相当柔软 看 看
She was some yoga teacher, proper bendy. Look. Look.
天哪 该死的 怎么 她把这个发送给你了 对吗
Jesus! Fuck! What, she sent that to you, did she?
真淘气
Double naughty.
起开
Jog on.
林兹
Linds!
林兹 我的手提电脑在哪
Linds, where's my laptop?
- 别这么扫兴 - 用你自己的
- Don't be a bell end! - Use your own.
- 我的坏了 反正你的也卡死了 - 你做了什么
- Mine's bust. Yours has gone all frozen anyway. - What did you do?
- 我只是想装这个看电影的东东 - 什么看电影
- I was trying to put on this film thing.- What film thing?
不知道 一个可以让你免费看电影的软件
Don't know. Some programme lets you watch free films.
我装上去的时候 它就卡死了
While I was trying to put it on, then it locked up.
- 诶 这不是我的错 - 不要再拿走它了 又不是你的
- Look, it's not my fault. - Don't take it again. It's not yours.
- 哦 你弄好了修一下我的吧 - “你弄好了修一下我的吧”
- Oh, fix mine when you've done that. - "Fix mine when you've done that."
（重启中）
（免费下载）
（下载中）
（正在诊断 清理并删除恶意软件）
- 不要刮花我的钢板 - 管它呢
- Stop nicking my Cokes! - Whatever.
那是你画的吗 肯尼
Did you draw that yourself, Kenny?
肯尼 谢谢 明天见
Thanks, Kenny. See you tomorrow.
再见
Bye.
- 拜 肯尼 - 拜 肯尼 明天见
- Bye, Kenny. - Bye, Kenny, I'll see you tomorrow.
你疯了吧
You're mental.
- 你疯了 - 你是个小偷
- You're mental. - You're a thief.
亲爱的 肯尼 你觉得怎么样
Love? Kenny? What do you think?
- 我还是有点不习惯这个颜色 - 挺不错的
- I'm still not used to the colour. - It's nice.
是么
Yeah?
可以帮我个忙 好好看着你妹妹吗
Do me a favour and prison-guard your sister, will you?
我不会太晚回来的 应该吧
I won't be late. Probably.
哦 天啊 他已经在门口了 冰箱里有千层面
Oh, my God! He's outside.There's a lasagna thing in the freezer.
我爱你
I love you.
（我们看到你干了什么）
（回复你的电话号码 不然我们就把这个视频 发给你所有的联系人）
（您的邮件已发送）
（一条未知信息）
（保持定位服务开启状态）
（保持开机并充好电）
（等时机成熟 你会被启用）
（你是谁）
（你想要钱吗）
（不要告诉任何人）
（我们在监视着你）
你看到我的钥匙了吗
Have you seen my keys?
你还好吧 肯 亲爱的
You okay, Ken? Love?
嗯 我很好
Yeah, fine.
- 早上好 肯尼 - 嗨
- Morning, Kenny. - Hi.
（一条未知信息）
（你已经被启用）
（服从指示 不然我们就泄露视频）
（到这里去 中午12点）
（工业区 黑石街）
（我在上班）
（45分钟之内到 不然我们就泄露视频）
- 肯尼 - 我觉得很难受
- Kenny? - Feeling really sick.
- 你才来而已 - 我知道 可是我觉得我要吐了
- You've only just got here. - I know but think I might throw up.
好吧 下一次你能不能
Okay, just next time can you…?
喂 莫激动啊 蠢货
Whoa! Easy, knobber.
（还有六公里 到达）
（不要迟到 你还有90秒）
（我到了）
（等着）
快拿着
Come on.
- 这是易碎物品 - 这是什么
- It's fragile. - What is it?
他们让我这么干的
They told me to do that.
就这样吗 我现在该做什么
Is that it? What do I do now?
我真的帮不了你
I can't really help you.
我要做些什么
What do I have to do?
不管他们说什么 你只要干了 就结束了
Just whatever they say and once you've done that, you're out.
他们放过你了
They let you off.
（确认收到包裹 核实包裹上的数字）
（把包裹送到这里 121房）
谁阿
Hello?
快 快递
Del… Delivery.
送错房间了
Wrong room.
他们说121房
They said 121.
不是 这里没有定快递
No, there's no delivery here.
- 可是他们说 - 我什么都没有定
- But they said… - I haven't ordered anything.
是个蛋糕
It's a cake.
- 什么蛋糕 - 不知道 我猜是个海绵蛋糕
- What cake? - I don't know. I think it's a sponge.
我没有订蛋糕 你把它送回蛋糕店
I didn't order a cake so just take it back to the bakery.
- 告诉他们弄错了 - 嗨 如果我
- and tell them they got it wrong. - Look, if I…
我不想要蛋糕 你再不走我就叫前台了
I don't want the cake.So go away or I call the front desk.
（他不开门）
（说是明迪让你来的）
我要把蛋糕踢进你的屁股里
I will kick that cake up your fucking arse.
明迪让我来的
M-Mindy sent me.
- 这是什么 明迪在哪 - 他们只是叫我把这个送给你
- What is this? Where's Mindy? - I was just told to give this to you.
- 明迪告诉你的吗 - 不是
- Mindy told you? - No.
- 你刚刚说“明迪” - 是他们叫我这么说的
- You said "Mindy." - That's what they told me to say.
进来
Get inside.
所以你说什么 你说明迪定了个蛋糕
So what are you saying?Are you saying Mindy ordered the cake?
不 呃 我不知道 是 他们 是他们
No, uh, I don't know.It… they… it was them.
他们 他们 你到底是干嘛的
Them? They? Who the fuck are you on about?
- 那些人 - 他妈的哪些人
- The people. - What fucking people?
手机里的人 电话里的人
The phone people.The people on the phone.
他们让我带蛋糕来 他们给我发信息
They told me to bring the cake, and they're leaving texts on my phone,
- 然后我就按照他们说的做了 - 喂 喂 慢点说
- and then I do what they say. - Whoa, whoa. Slow down.
用鼻子呼吸
Just breathe through your nose.
用鼻子 好吗
Through your nose. Okay?
好的 现在 让我看看他们说了什么 给我你手机
Good. Now, just show me what they said. On your phone.
- 给我看信息 - 好的 嗯 嗯 这个
- Show me the text. - Okay, well, um… This.
- 我应该 - 闭嘴 让我来
- I should…- Shut up. Just let me.
这是什么鬼
What the fuck is this?
- 他们是谁 - 我不知道
- Who are these people? - I don't know.
- 你是谁 - 我和他们不是一伙的
- Who are you? - I'm not them.
他们给我发信息 我就按他们说的做
They send me messages, and I do what they say.
为什么 你为什么要那样做
Why? Why would you do that?
是他们吗
Is it them?
（我现在可以走了吗）
（拍张他的照片）
- 他们说我一定要这么做 - 上帝啊
- They said I had to do that. - Jesus Christ!
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
他们说我们一定要按照他们的指示
They're saying they just need us to follow their instructions,
这样一切都没问题了 好吗
and everything will be okay. Okay?
该死
Shit!
他们说我们要一起做
They're saying we have to do it together.
- 我们要干什么 - 把蛋糕带到一个地方
- What do we have to do? - Just take the cake somewhere.
他们给了我一个地址 一个地图坐标之类的东西
They sent me an address.A map coordinate thing.
- 我们还要找一辆车 - 一辆车 什么样的车
- And there's a car we need to get.- A car? What sort of car?
我不知道要什么样的车 他们说在外面停着的车里
I don't know what sort of car.They said it's in the car park outside.
他们给了我一个车牌号 我就知道这么多了
They sent me a licence plate.That's all I know.
为什么要我们两个一起
Why both of us?
我不知道
I don't know!
先让我搞定这该死的鞋子 好吗
Just let me deal with myfucking shoe, please.
（和他一起走 带上包裹）
他们说了什么
What have they said?
他们说 “和他一起去 带上包裹”
They say, "Go with him.Take the package."
好的
Okay.
这些该死的号码看得我眼都瞎了
I'm getting fucking number blindness here.
是这个
That's it.
好的 他们说钥匙在这后面 好吧
All right. They said the keys are on the back. Okay.
听着 也许你开车会比较好 你会开车吗
Look, maybe you better drive. Do you drive?
- 你看 我刚刚喝酒了 - 我不会开 不我会 我只会一点
- I mean, I had a drink back there. - I can't. I can… I can drive.
我还在学 还没通过考试
I'm still learning. Haven't passed my test yet.
好吧 那你来导航
All right. Uh… You're navigating.
你手机里有卫星定位吗
Okay, you've got a sat nav on your phone?
有
Yep.
这是那个位置 把它输进去
Here it is. Punch that in.
是一条城郊的街 叫什么海威科姆什么玩意的
It's a street somewhere out of town.Sort of High Wycombe-ish.
他们让我们俩得一起去 时间不多了
They said we got to be there by two. It's gonna be tight.
我猜他们也抓着你什么破把柄威胁着要公开吧
So I'm guessing they got some shit on you that they're threatening to put out?
我的把柄是
With me, it's…
你在房间里看见的 该死的蕾丝内裤
You saw the room, fucking lacy knickers.
我当时在等一个妓女
I was waiting for a prostitute.
或者说三陪 鸡 不管人们现在究竟怎么称呼她们
Escort, hooker, whatever they call them now.
我有家室 幸福美满
I got a family, which is great.
你还听无聊了啊
You get bored.
遥想我年轻的时候 我曾经
I mean, when I was young, I used to like…
我也不好辩解 我就想和二十几岁的人搞一次
I can't fucking justify it. I just wanted to fuck a 20-something.
想重温下青葱岁月吧 我也不知道
For old times' sake, I don't know.
我加入了这个网站 我只是好奇 想看看它到底有啥
I joined this website. I was curious. Just wanted to see what was on there.
我就和明迪聊了天 当然是我以为她是明迪
I got talking to Mindy, who I thought was Mindy.
她给我发了她的照片 我也发回了些我的照片
I mean, she sent me pictures. I sent some back.
拿手机拍的 抓着我的老二
Phone photos. Grabbing my cock.
你懂的 他们就拍到了全过程
You name it. They got the whole fucking thing.
还不仅仅是照片 聊天信息啥的 还有约会内容 什么时候啥地点
But not just pictures, chat messages. All the arrangements, where and when.
我向他们讨价还价 他们只说他们手上啥都有
Me haggling over the price and they say they got it all.
像审计那帮人样 抓着辫子不放
Sucked up the whole hard drive like an audit.
该死的贱货 真特么该死的混蛋
Fucking twat. What a fucking idiot!
如果这些东西流出去了 我老婆就会跟我离婚了
If that shit gets out, that's my wife out the door.
还有我的孩子们 她应该也会带走
Then there's the kids, she'll take them.
哦不 她肯定会把孩子带走 然后还会赢
Oh, no, not a doubt in my mind she'd take them and she'd win.
赢得孩子的抚养权
Custody, she'd win.
但我不会失去我的孩子们的 我跟你讲
And I'm not losing my kids. I tell you that right now.
绝不会 绝对特么的不会的
No way! Absolutely fucking no!
他们拍我
They filmed me.
- 拍你 - 通过我电脑摄像头
- Filmed you… - Through my computer camera.
- 啥 就像 录像吗 - 是的 就在干那个的时候 你懂的
- What, like, filmed you? - Yeah, like, you know, doing it.
- 做爱的时候吗 - 不是 是 那个
- Like sex? - No. Like, you… you know.
手淫 看片手淫吧
Jerking off. Jerking off to porn or something?
可人人都这么干啊
Well, everyone does that.
- 连教皇还这么干呢 - 他们要把视频公开
- The fucking pope probably does that. - They're gonna put it everywhere.
他们要把视频发给每个人
Like they're gonna send it to everyone.
- 哎我去 麻了个蛋的 - 怎么了怎么了
- Oh, shit the fuck! - What? What?
- 那灯闪了多久了 - 什么灯
- How long's that light been on? - What light?
不管车是谁的 居然他妈的没加油
Whoever's car this is，they left it fucking empty.
我马上回来
I won't be a minute.
无铅的 无铅的
Unleaded. Unleaded.
靠 混蛋
Oh, bugger!
听着 你去交钱 这样省时间
Listen, you pay, yeah? It'll save time.
你带钱了吗
Have you got any money?
好吧 银联卡 密码3109 你重复一遍
Okay, Visa card PIN number 3109. Say that back to me.
- 银联卡 - 就密码
- Visa card… - Just the number!
- 嗯 3109 - 去吧
- Uh… 3109. - Okay, go!
四号油泵哈
Pump four!
- 几号泵 - 四号
- What's your pump number? - Four.
- 想要点巧克力吗 - 不用了
- You want some chocolate? - No.
- 这周半价哦 - 不用了
- It's two for one this week. - I'm okay.
31.89
31.89.
输入你的密码
Pop your PIN in.
- 你确定你不介意吧 - 不会当然不会
- If you're sure you don't mind? - No, no, of course not.
- 我会办的 打几个电话 - 太棒了 记着是下周三
- I'll get on to that. Make some calls. - Brilliant! It's next Wednesday.
- 好的 - 最好是非乳制的 保险起见
- Okay. - Keep it non-dairy just to be safe.
好的
Okay.
这位是 额
This is, uh…
我侄子
my nephew.
你好
Nice to meet you.
- 我叫肯尼 - 你好肯尼 我是凯伦
- Kenny. - Kenny. I'm Karen.
我俩都是K打头啊
We're both Ks.
我是西奥和凯西学校的家长教师会主管 真是自作自受
I'm head of the PTA at Theo and Cassie's school, for my sins.
我刚刚在说服可怜的赫克托为猜谜之夜准备餐厅
Just roped poor Hector into sorting out the catering for the quiz night.
那一般会留下一团糟
Been the usual balls up.
额 我得把这孩子快点送去车站
Listen, we better get this guy to the station.
他的火车快开了 所以我们最好先撤了
His train's… So we better go.
- 是坎斯路的车站吗 - 是的
- Cansroad Station? - Yeah.
那你们能不能顺便载我去下我家那条路
Oh, couldn't drop me at the end of my road, could you?
顺路的 迈耶尔街
It's on the way. Mayer Street?
要不我就得等公交 它走的也是一样的线路
It's the bus otherwise and that goes all the way around the common.
- 我们其实有点赶 - 哦你们不会绕远路的 就是顺路
- We're in a bit of a rush, actually. - Well, it's no detour. It's en route.
你们都不用减速 我会自己跳下去的 可以吗
I'll hop out. Hardly need to slow down. Yeah?
- 当然 上车吧 - 太棒了 谢谢
- Yep. Sure. Let's go. - Brilliant. Thanks!
我坐后面
I'll just get in the back.
哦 我不想压到你们的盒子
Oh, don't want to squash your box.
- 这是什么 礼物吗 - 是块蛋糕
- What's that? Present? - It's a cake.
- 给佩妮的蛋糕 - 哦 她真幸运
- It's just a… it's a cake for Penny. - Oh, lucky her.
佩妮最近怎么样
So how is Penny?
自从大概上次运动会后就一直没见过她了
Haven't seen her since… must have been sports day.
她很好
She's good.
- 她还准备着回去工作吗 - 是的
- She still planning to get back to work? - Yeah. Yep.
（我们看见你们的定位了）
- 西奥今年多大了 - 额 七岁
- I mean, how old's Theo now? - Uh… He's seven.
（钥匙在后车轮的上面）
他在表演里演得有趣极了 戴着个又大又高的帽子
He was so funny in the play. That big top hat on.
是啊 他很享受
Yeah, he had a good time.
（你们走错路了）
哦对了 安娜要举办个睡衣派对
Oh, Anna's having a sleepover.
凯西应该已经告诉你了
Cassie's probably already told you about it.
一间屋子里挤六个九岁的小屁孩儿 我一定是疯了
Six nine-year-olds in the house. I must be mad!
（调头）
肯尼你要去哪里呢
So, Kenny, where you heading back to?
- 对不起 你刚说什么 - 你是回家还是去哪里
- Sorry. What? - Are you going home or…?
- 额 - 培训 在伯明翰
- Uh… - Train. Birmingham.
额 对
Yeah. Uh…
- 嗯 我住在伯明翰 - 哦 我丈夫是从伯明翰来的
- Yeah, I-I live in Birmingham. - Oh, my husband's from Birmingham.
- 你住在哪个地区 - 南区
- What part are you? - South.
南区
South.
- 大概 - 这样啊
- Mainly. - Right.
（调头）
你一直住在那里吗 因为你口音好像不像
Have you always lived there? Cos you don't sound…
我没有口音 人人都这么说
I don't have the accent, no. Everyone says that…
说我没什么口音
That… I don't have the accent.
我不在那里长大 我小时候住在其他地方
Didn't grow up there though. I grew up somewhere else.
比如伦敦 我在伦敦长大
Like London. I grew up in London.
这样哦
Okay.
（不然我们就公开一切）
那你父母是赫克托这边的还是佩妮那边的
And is your mum and dad on Hector's side or Penny's?
有人过马路 他要过马路
Someone crossing! Crossing!
实在抱歉 不能耽误他的火车
Sorry about that! Can't miss his train.
到我家了
This is me.
肯尼 很高兴见到你 代我向佩妮问好
Great to meet you, Kenny. Give my best to Penny, won't you?
- 好的 - 那么 再见
- Yes, of course. - Bye, then.
- 再见 凯伦 - 再见
- Bye, Karen. - Bye.
我们会准时到的 好吗
We're gonna make it, okay?
好像是这个路口
It's this junction.
- 啥 这个吗 - 是的 是的
- What? This one? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你确定这里就是
You sure this is it?
“打开蛋糕看看”
"Look in the cake."
我们打开看看
Let's look in the cake.
打开蛋糕看看
Look in the cake.
在蛋糕里面吧 我猜
In the cake, I suppose.
我抓到什么了
I got something.
这是啥玩意儿
What the fuck?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
“给你们五分钟时间考虑”
"Five minutes to decide."
考虑啥
Decide what?
- “谁开车” - “谁去抢”
- "Who is driver?" - "Who is robber?"
（国家联合银行）
哦 不
Oh, no. No.
- 我 我 我们 不不不行 - 我来开车
- W-w-we can't. We… - I'm driver.
你说你不能开车 我来开车
You said you can't drive. I'm driver.
我不熄火 在这里等你
I'll be right here with the engine running.
我们 不能这样做 我们
We… We can't. We…
那么我们还能怎么做 肯尼
Then how else are we gonna deal with this, Kenny?
- 我不会 - 听我说
- I'm not… - Listen to me.
- 我不会 - 闭嘴安静听我说
- I'm not… - Shut up and listen!
有帽子和墨镜 没人会认出你来的
Hat and sunglasses. No one's going to ID you.
你甚至可以是凯文·贝肯 这是第一点
You could be Kevin fucking Bacon. That's point one.
安静 第二 一般抢劫中 银行职员都是受过训练的
Shut up! Point two, in a robbery, staff are trained.
我不能
I am not…
他们受训如何交出现金
They are trained to hand over the cash.
没有争执 我看纪录片是这么拍的 没有反抗 看起来挺简单的
No argument. I saw it in a documentary. No resistance. It looked easy.
一点都不简单
It's not easy.
我知道不简单 但我们还能做什么呢 嘿
I know it isn't easy, but what the fuck else are we gonna do? Hey?
如果这个传出去了 我会失去我的孩子
This gets out, I will lose my kids.
我发誓 如果真发生了 我就去厨房
And I swear to God, I will stand in the kitchen.
拿面包刀朝我脖子来一刀
and put a fucking bread knife through my throat if that happens.
- 我只是看看照片 - 然后在镜头前手淫
- I only looked at pictures and… - And beat one off on camera?
这是他们掌控的把柄了
That's what they got, yeah?
你那发红的小脸 脏不拉几的小手 四溅的精液
Your hot little face, blurred fist, dick burping fucking spunk everywhere?
你妈妈肯定会喜欢在脸书 推特还有in什么来着上面看见你那样
Your mum's gonna love that on Facebook, Twitter, Insta-fucking-whatever.
还有她的朋友 所有人都能看到 你这样那样
And her friends. All eyes on you, giving it that.
更别说上班时那些混蛋同事会叫你小精虫
Toss in the cunts at work, calling you Spurty McGoo.
嘲笑你的高潮脸 把它当桌面
Laughing at your come face, making it their desktop wallpaper.
可不只接下来几周 几年可能都是这样
It's not just weeks. We're talking years here.
上传到谷歌的图片就像吉普赛的诅咒
Pictures hang about on Google like a gypsy fucking curse.
互联网不给人重来的机会 这事可没完
There's no cure for the Internet. It would never go away.
这事会一直跟着你 一生的污点
It'd be glued to your name, a fucking stain on you.
如果是我的话 我就去上吊
I'd hang myself if that was me.
一有机会我就扭断自己脖子
Crack my fucking neck at the first opportunity.
他们只是要钱 那就走进去然后抢钱
They just want the money, so go in there and do it.
- 你会开走的 - 我不会开走的
- You'll drive away. - I am not gonna drive away.
我就坐在这里 发动机我都不关
I'm gonna be sat here with the engine running.
我不行 我不行
I can't. I can't.
- 你可以的 可以的 - 我不行 我不行 不行不行
- You can. You can. - I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.
- 你可以的 - 我不行
- You can. - I can't.
我们时间不多了 肯尼
We don't have much time, Kenny.
- 这不是真的 这不是真的 - 你可以的
- It's not real. This is not real. - You can do this.
振作起来 镇定点 求你了
Keep it together. Please hold it together.
- 闭嘴 闭嘴 闭嘴 - 好吧
- Shut up, shut up, shut up! Shut up! - Okay.
你带了包么
Have you got a bag?
眼睛 用鼻子呼吸
Glasses. Breathe through your nose.
给我钱
Give me money.
赶紧给我钱
Just give me money!
- 好的 好 - 很多 我需要很多钱
- Yes. Okay. - Lots of it. I need lots of it.
我 我应该用你的包么
Sh-should I use your bag?
拿着
Take it.
我现在把包还给你 这样可以么
I'm going to pass this back to you now. Is that okay?
站在那里打电话的一个伙计吓到我了
There was some bloke standing there on his phone freaking me out.
- 你拿到了吗 - 嗯
- Did you get it? - Yeah.
开快点
Go faster.
限速40 你想因为超速被拦下来吗
Speed limit's 40. Wanna get stopped for speeding now?
- 哦 天哪 - 妈的
- Oh, shit. - Fuck!
有警笛声
That's a siren.
嘘 小声点
Shh! Shush.
- 快走 - 闭嘴
- Let's go! - Shut up.
等等 等等
Wait, wait.
拜托
Come on.
好
Okay.
没事的
We're okay.
我们应该给他们发短信 是吧 告诉他们我们拿到钱了
We should text them, no? Tell them we got the money.
- 他们说我们要拿着钱去某个地方 - 什么地方
- They say we got to take it somewhere. - Where?
就这里
This is it.
嗯
Yeah.
好嘞
Here we go.
“最后的指令”
"Final instruction."
“把车开走然后销毁”
"Take car away and destroy."
毁车
Destroy the car.
“就你一个人去”
"Just you alone."
为什么只是你一个人
Why just you?
（把钱拿到指定地点）
（一个人去）
我得把钱拿去那儿
I got to take the money somewhere over there.
为什么 为什么总是我
Why? Why have I got to do it?
鬼知道
Fuck knows.
所以
So…
你最好赶紧去
You better go, yeah?
嘿 你都走到这一步了 不是吗
Hey, you got this far, haven't you?
把包扔在那里就好了 就结束了
Just drop it off. That's it.
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
嘿 听着 肯尼 听着 我很抱歉 刚刚
Hey, listen, Kenny. Look. I'm sorry about… just back there.
吵你大声嚷嚷 骂了你
Shouting at you. Calling you stuff.
我这人很正常的 我发誓 当一切
I'm an all right bloke really. I swear I am, when it's…
当一切比较正常的时候
When stuff's normal.
你自己当心 好吧
You take care, yeah?
嗯嗯 等等 等等
Yeah, yeah. Hang on, hang on.
他告诉我要先启动这个
They told me I had to set this thing off first.
好的
Okay.
你得到奖金了吗
You got the prize money?
- 奖金 - 就是那个 打架那个
- Prize money? - You know, for the… fight?
什么打架
How is there a fight?
- 他们没跟你说吗 - 没有
- They didn't tell you? - No.
我们得打一架
We've got to fight…
不然的话他们会把手里的把柄全都发到网上去
…or else they post everything they've got on us.
胜者得到钱
Winner takes the money.
打架在所难免了
We've got to do it.
我的意思是
I mean…
他们在看着呢
They're watching.
什么样的架 我们怎么知道何时结束
What sort of fight? How do we know when it's over?
我们 我们怎么判断输赢
How… How do we know who's won?
我不知道你什么情况 但我如果这个泄露出去我的人生就完蛋了
I don't know about you, but my life's over if this gets out.
真他妈完蛋了
Fucking over.
他们手上有你什么把柄
What they get you for?
我只是看了几张照片
I just looked at some photos.
就是这样了 我只是看了一两张照片
That's all. I just looked at one or two photos.
是
Yeah.
是是 我也只是看了照片
Yeah, yeah, I just looked at pictures too.
照片里面的她们几岁啊 有多小
How young were they? In the pictures?
有多小
How young?
嗯
Yeah.
嗯 我也是
Well, me too.
（现在 打架）
（用死判定输赢）
看 朋友 别 求你了
Look, mate. Don't. Please.
求你了
Please.
拜托
深呼吸
Breathe…
明迪
Mindy?
（CEO深陷“种族歧视电子邮件”丑闻）
你已经沦落到这种地步了吗
Is that what you've become?
- 肮脏恶心的变态 - 嘿 放轻松
- A dirty, sick, disgusting pervert? - Hey, relax!
看着我 你是这种人吗
Look at me! Is that what you are?
肯尼 你做了什么啊 他们说那还是孩子啊
What did you do, Kenny? They're saying it's kids!
那是小孩子的照片
That you've been looking at kids!
林德赛看见了 网上有你的视频
And Lindsey saw it. There's a video of you.
她所有的朋友都看到了
All of her friends have got it!
孩子啊 肯尼 告诉我这不是真的
Kids, Kenny! Tell me that's not true!